<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Comtom's</title>
 <link href="http://getpoole.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://getpoole.com/"/>
 <updated>2014-04-01T14:48:05-03:00</updated>
 <id>http://getpoole.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Tomas Gonzalez Dowling</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Building responsive apps</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2014/04/03/building-responsive-apps/"/>
   <updated>2014-04-03T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2014/04/03/building-responsive-apps</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What? Is Flappy Bird Android App offline?</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2014/02/12/is-flappy-bird-app-offline/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-12T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2014/02/12/is-flappy-bird-app-offline</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No way! Why would someone that’s being so successfull with a particular app and doing thousands of dolars each day with ads, retire it from play store and App Store. That doesn’t make any sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But instead of speculating about ‘why that guy did what he did’ like de 99.99% of other blogs, I’m sharing the game with all of you, games junkies :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mega.co.nz/#!7ZVDXTwJ!KsYnR7azugiySntNvsK083LFC4cqs8TbqHxtTHLQ-8w&quot;&gt;Download Free &amp;amp; Original Flappy Bird for Andoid (APK)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Jekyll on board</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2014/01/04/jekyll-onboard/"/>
   <updated>2014-01-04T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2014/01/04/jekyll-onboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New year, new blogging plattform&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been using Wordpress for a while, but it was a hedeache to update and I didn&amp;#39;t use a lot of features, I always felt that it was too big for me. Then I found Tumblr, wich worked fine, but also it was a little big, since I didn&amp;#39;t use the social features. Also Tumblr had a lot of stability issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you probably know, less is more, so I choose &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; this time, the static site generator. It&amp;#39;s a small but it makes a site very fast and reliable as it generates all html only when you decide it. It includes among other features templates, pages and posts, nothing really to envy to Wordpress or others &lt;bigger&gt; competitors as you don&amp;#39;t need to use a database or run a script on each visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Drawbacks&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll does not provide a commments system, so I chose Disqus, a free comments service that it&amp;#39;s realy easy to integrate, and it&amp;#39;s really nice to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;More software&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve found Poole, a more easy way to implement Jekyll. It&amp;#39;s developed on and hosted with GitHub. Head to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; for downloads, bug reports, and features requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I&amp;#39;m used to work with git repositories, and all modifications are tracked, so any mistake would be easily recovered, also I can use the repository as a backup, so the same process of modifing content will record that change on the git database and each time I make a push, that data will be stored in a remote host. When the push is finished, a git hook is triggered and then all the files are updated in the webserver so with a very simple to use system, I can resolv the three problems: backup generation, deploying website updates or new content and keeping track of what is modified (and who did that modification).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoyed this article, keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What's Jekyll?</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2013/12/31/whats-jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2013-12-31T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2013/12/31/whats-jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator, an open-source tool for creating simple yet powerful websites of all shapes and sizes. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll/blob/master/README.markdown&quot;&gt;the project&amp;#39;s readme&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory [...] and spits out a complete, static website suitable for serving with Apache or your favorite web server. This is also the engine behind GitHub Pages, which you can use to host your project’s page or blog right here from GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an immensely useful tool and one we encourage you to use here with Hyde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out more by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;visiting the project on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>BBM for iOS and Android (now officially) is out!</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2013/10/28/BBM-for-android-is-out/"/>
   <updated>2013-10-28T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2013/10/28/BBM-for-android-is-out</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blackberry Limited just released blackberry messenger app for apple and Android mobile plattforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try it out and tell us what you thik.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rim.mobilefusion.client&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/es/app/bbm/id690046600?ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An error notification comes in that is related to code you worked on</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2013/02/09/an-error-notification-comes-in-that-is-related-to-code-you-worked-on/"/>
   <updated>2013-02-09T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2013/02/09/an-error-notification-comes-in-that-is-related-to-code-you-worked-on</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/An059.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Go, Arnold!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Corporate website updates</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2012/02/18/corporate-website-updates/"/>
   <updated>2012-02-18T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2012/02/18/corporate-website-updates</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Website updates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we released a brand new corporate site, you can see it in action at &lt;a href=&quot;https://comtomtech.com&quot;&gt;comtomtech.com&lt;/a&gt;
Hope you like it :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More changes are to come, so stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
